but you know last time you were here you
were in a relationship you had a a a a
real that went viral on this show and
people really loved what you were saying
and one of the things you said in it was
until you never experienced a [ __ ] try
I have never experienced until being
with I have never experienced a [ __ ]
try that's never one not one never it's
true and then I experienced a [ __ ] stop
[Laughter]
trying and I know [ __ ] in the comments
right now like see that's why she's
single and it's like yeah that is
exactly why I'm single because we live
in a society that hasn't caught up to
women like me as black people like we
just aren't really taught how to love
ourselves like we don't even know what
that looks like a lot of times like I
think so many of us are in that process
on a regular basis like what does that
actually mean why can't we support each
other and know that you have your
strengths and I have my strengths like
you're [ __ ] balls does not give you
leadership skills the idea that you
would trust someone to birth the baby
that you would give everything to but
not to handle your feelings is Bonkers
but it's also like women we also need to
be very practiced at how to handle
feelings I okay will cry for you
tonight that's why when people say wild
[ __ ] to me like a man hates black men
I'm like check my record you know you
know how the politicians be like check
my voting record I'm like check my money
record okay
hey guys welcome back
to shout out to all our real lovers out
there hi everybody welcome back welcome
back Rhonda you want to tell them where
we're at today o I do because we are in
a very nice looking place I know y'all
see all the fixtures all the things I
just want to shout out the fine fine
fine folks at City Ridge Apartment we so
appreciate you sponsoring this episode
if you are in the market for a beautiful
luxurious DC home please visit City Rd
dc.com and Erica you know I love you I
appreciate you we appreciate you guys so
much beautiful spot beautiful spot it's
very sexy yeah it's very sexy in here so
before we get started if welcome if
you're new here um you're now part of
the real lover gang and to officially be
initiated just hit the Subscribe button
that's it the show said just hit the
Subscribe button that like share you got
to do like seven things to get in gang
yeah you you just and what they call it
when when uh frat preliminaries I don't
know yeah you you got just a me and
greet face yeah and then you got to go
through all the initiations then you got
to write a review and then once you do
that gang gang there we go then you gang
gang there we go well today special day
uh what you call it Ronda our first
second yes our first second explain that
to them so this very special guest has
already been a guest but she was also
our first guest yes and now she's our
first part two do you feel special I
didn't know I was the first guest yes I
did know I was the first yes
you welcome back Amanda
Amanda you said every time you in DC DC
treats you well how's DC been thus far
on your trip fabulous DC really treats
me well now I have I have the radio show
here in DC so you can listen to the
Amanda seals show 10 to3 on Magic in DC
you also listen to it wherever you get
your podcast um but it's a syndicated
radio show so I mean it's all over the
nation but to be on the air in DC which
has always been like a market that's
shown me so much love like it really
means a lot so you know I am happy to be
here we're happy to have you here and I
will say with we have our friendship
we're working with Amanda Amanda is just
amazing oh
Dre like it's it's amazing to see it
from the outside but when you're on the
inside and see how somebody works too
it's just like hard working black
woman I appreciate that no problem no
problem so you here for the second time
yes uh I think we have to
address uh we wouldn't call it an
elephant in the room but you know last
time you were here you were in a
relationship and I want to quote you had
a a a a real that went viral on this
show oh I did yeah yeah it
went and people really loved what you
were saying and one of the things you
said in it was
until you never experienced a [ __ ] try
but I have been with people who were
like not gonna let me go but they also
weren't trying to improve so like what
are we really doing I have never
experienced until being with I have
never experienced a [ __ ] try that's
never one not one never it's true and
then I experienced a [ __ ] stop
trying so last time you on to show you
were in a relationship but shortly after
you were no longer in one and you did it
creatively on Instagram the announcement
was very creative Rhonda actually sent
it to first loved very creative we
should probably plug that real like in
right here so you can just see too good
how you announce
that Amanda alert Amanda
alert Amanda alert Amanda alert Amanda
alert Amanda
alert that's not cute that is not cute
all right y'all listen up got some big
news here at the Amanda seals troll
Center looks like she is no longer in a
relationship and has been relegated back
to the street streets tough break isn't
that a shame I'm not
surprised she always running the damn
mouth you know okay ain't nobody trying
to hear all that running that
mouth black love loses again can we call
it black love I mean they was both light
skinn I told you she can't keep a man I
told y'all I told y'all she can't keep a
man what I say I bet wanted a white
woman right now she knows it's for the
fled and that the high power is always
working in her favor but you know they
had build a life together so uh it's
going to take some time for her to heal
and recenter
herself so it's the perfect time to
really get in that ass exactly so I need
y'all to get focused on natur stations
okay k k Kens what you got well me and
the C of Karens uh we can get busy
saying that this happened because she's
always talking this black stuff like
that I'm sure even he started hearing
about it cracker this cracker that
Cracker Box Cracker Jacks white Jesus
black Jesus white Santa Black Santa the
blood is still red the suit is still
red the states are still red okay Becky
okay she probably can't even cook am I
right probably cooking rice in a rice
cooker okay all right now how about you
black woman who only reads blog
headlines and believes them me and my #
squeal Squad we we going to drop in them
DMS and remind her that she's a failure
and she should never talk about
relationships
again where she now you know she BL me
she always running her mouth she thinks
she a man
exactly a real queen wouldn't have so
much to
say how can she be a queen if she thinks
she a king I see you black
man I see you Queen I see you King I see
you good good [ __ ] good [ __ ] all right
brother hotep what you got well it seems
like the correct thing to do is put
together a series of videos that defame
her the first being one that labels her
a narcissist the second being her uh
continual perpetuation of the gay agenda
going from sister to supporting sis and
the third of course concluding with a
false and erroneous projection of her as
one who hates black
men oh they Ain put that on the blog yet
you see the is how I found out that the
vaccine was turning everybody gay that
gay agenda and she be down with that she
a the same one talking about we need to
be called Sis jender Sis focus on
getting you a [ __ ] brother hotel that
seems like quite a tall order you're
going to be able to pull that off by
yourself you do got a point there uh let
me call on my H Breen
all right everybody looks like we got
our plans and placees time to lock in
for operation beat a [ __ ] while she's
down
wo no if you B on a heart
yeah
[ __ ] great idea great plan be I don't
got nothing better to do never liked her
never you know she got me y got me
[ __ ] up
but I think people just want to know
what
happened oh
um well that little thing you know what
it is
it's it's always interesting when you're
on a healing process like if you're
constantly in a healing process then you
are constantly becoming more aware of
things that you may not have been aware
of before like even in listening to that
that makes me cringe that a [ __ ] trying
was enough that was the standard like
that's wild to me like hearing you say
that back is like oh my God you hear the
I'm over here heavy breathing like cuz I
have been there yeah like and I think a
lot of women who are so like you started
out this podcast by saying like Amanda
works so hard like you know she's like
really you know on her [ __ ] Etc and I
think a lot of women like myself suffer
from Smart wom dumb girl syndrome
explain that oh girl I will leave this
room
and what I consider smart women dumb
girl syndrome to be is that we are like
book smart we are even like um we are
Savvy like we might be business yeah but
we're not heart smart so and that
doesn't mean that you don't have
emotional intelligence what that means
is that like there really is a dynamic
to like being in relationships with like
cisgendered heterosexual men that like
some women have mastered and that are
able to understand and like if you
didn't have the right people around you
like growing up you kind of never like
learned those skills you know like I
have a lot of skills I never had those
skills I was also flat chested till like
98 so like I was also like a late
bloomer yeah um and so there's just a
constant work in progress around like my
own now mind you I can see somebody
else's easy clear as day 2020 even
actually more than 2020 I'm like Jordy
on Star Trek with the visor like I can
actually see better than all of y'all
you know but when it's my own self which
is the norm like your own self like you
don't have the same ability but I feel
like what really happened was that
I like crossed over into a space
of um maturity that like my partner just
did not want to go to and that ended up
being a catalyst for seeing like a lot
of other things that I hadn't really
maybe not allowed myself to be before
but that I didn't consider to be deal
breakers before but if you don't want to
grow up that's a deal breaker we have to
grow we have to grow
and
um you know I think
that the biggest lesson I learned
was what it looks like when someone
loves thems
h that's a good and just as black people
like we just aren't really taught how to
love ourselves like we don't even know
what that looks like a lot of times like
I think so many of us are in that
process on a regular basis like what
does that actually mean does it just
mean like going to get my nails done
like you know what I'm saying like
Audrey Lord talks about how like no like
loving yourself is loving your community
you know like loving yourself is being a
part of like creating the spaces that
you're in making them lovable right yeah
um and also like allowing the
possibility for you to experience Joy
allowing for you to heal there's work
that you have to do to do that and so a
lot of the brothers that I know that I
have dated like they have not actively
done that so if they're not even giving
themselves the opportunity to love
themselves and I'm not saying anything
new people have said this before but if
they're not giving themselves the
opportunity to love themselves in a real
way how can you possibly love someone
else not even just love me like that's
talk that's your kids like Etc anyone
you know yeah so that was like a real
like
like oh you're not even doing the things
for yourself yeah that would be
demonstrative of you loving yourself
like I know that I've had to go to
therapy because I'm like standing in the
way like I have trauma and I have
behaviors that are in the way of my
access to
Joy so then it's my responsibility y to
go and do that to go and do that yeah
and I I I brought some of that in our
relationship and it was in the way of
our joy in a relationship so I had to
actively work to like remove that yeah
from getting in the way of our joy in
our relationship but then if I remove it
and they still ain't joy in our
relationship with somebody up up we
process of
elimination both of us have to be on
that like did like and I think at the
end of the day like the [ __ ] didn't
like me why you say that
damn that was a that was a very sharp
summation a very sharp some me I
mean like grew to not or never did in
your assessment I don't know that he
ever did you think he was using you
mhm just playing the game as long as so
after after we broke up about a month
after we broke up I got a letter I got
an anonymous letter from somebody that
said that they had seen me on this
podcast this one this podcast this
podcast okay so shout out to y'all
hey and they were like oh um I saw you
on that podcast and you were saying that
you were in love with and you must be be
like the only person in the world that
didn't know that they were an
opportunist oh damn and then they went
on to to say a lot of things in this
letter that I'm not even going to share
here but they were all accurate and it
wasn't a scorned person that had been
with him before but it was somebody who
said I wanted to share this with you
because it's it's clear that you didn't
know
mhm and
um you know that it's you know just like
woman to woman I just wanted you to have
that knowledge and and again like I'm
not calling him an abuser like I'm not
saying any of those things right but at
the end of the day like opportunism
plays out in a number of different ways
and it can represent itself in
relationships in a myriad of ways
sometimes someone's an opportunity and
just that
like they just want to have somebody yep
yeah like they're not trying to clout
Chase necessarily they just want
partnership they want to float they want
to be floated and whatever that looks
like yes yeah I think it was more that
like I don't think he was clout chasing
but I think that this setup was probably
advantageous and comfortable um and I
desire to make the person I'm with
comfortable yeah right so like and
that's part of my own self low
self-esteem that's myown off and we
there's so many things that you said I
have a question about I want to go back
first is is when it comes to those men
that you were talking to did they see
that they had issues and were going
about their own way of trying to solve
them or they didn't think they had
issues at
all no I've always feel like I've dated
men
who for the most part acknowledge they
have issues and they've accepted it
about themselves like I'm not changing
this is just this is just who I
am and it feels like it's like it's
somehow for them a sense of
um I don't know it's like a source of
strength that I've accepted these flaws
it should be proud of me yeah like it's
come to terms with it and you know what
a lot of us do this thing where we have
been taught about this whole like making
lemons from making lemonade from lemons
type [ __ ] with our trauma and like
that's [ __ ] like making lemonade
from lemons is like oh I got stuck at
the beach so I made it a beach day you
know what I'm saying like making
lemonade from lemons isn't like my my
parents abandoned me and so you know now
I'm a real [ __ ] because I know how to
be abandoned like that's not making
lemonade from lemons right because also
a lot of times it's like you've accepted
a behavior that was never okay and you
didn't deserve that you didn't deserve
to be treated that way and whether you
want to judge them or not like that was
not how you should have been treated as
a child and you have to be able to
acknowledge that to be able to
acknowledge how it affected you and how
you are now carrying and perpetuating
through that so like even for myself
like my dad is whack and you know I have
abandonment issues because of that and
now I like respond to certain things a
certain way because of those abandonment
issues but I had to like be able to
grasp like oh this is because of this
and so I do that and that's in the way
of me getting this source of joy in
order to like move past it but that's
also like a ego thing you have to be
able to be willing to say like oh I'm
toxic
too I got to work on that I gotta work
on that it's funny one of the other
things you talked about which could have
been a part of thing but maybe not is
just like when you know that you are
going through your own stuff everything
that you just said your trauma you're
working on your stuff then you have a
partner that may feel like they don't
have all of that right like they don't
have trauma they don't or they they
haven't immediately Associated any I
feel like even still sometimes it's like
but you may still need outside help to
help me to support me you can't
necessarily fix my process like I have I
have my own process but you may not have
the tools to be my partner while I work
through my process like I still you
still have to be doing some work you
can't just think well you do that and
I'll be over here like I'll be K kicking
it and chilling while you work on your
stuff to me everyone needs to be working
on something my liftt might be heavier
right my I might have to carry way more
lumber but you need to be able to like
hold my back up while I'm doing it or
make sure there's nothing on the steps
like we have to be a team in order to
work through the things whatever the
things are if it's my things your things
whatever like I mean we I don't feel
like our society has like the tools like
we we're not taught that like I mean
some of us did like peer
counseling you know in middle school but
also everybody has trauma there's that
right so like there nobody is devoid of
um like even when white people be like
there's no such thing as white privilege
we all have traumas like that's not what
we're talking about but yes even you
rich Becky like you have trauma too
um but to me that is the biggest lie is
to tell yourself that you didn't have
trauma and the LIE of like n I'm good
yeah it's like but you're not like
you're not and that's okay like but in
order for that to work for both of us
like we got to acknowledge those things
and in the best case scenario I guess
like trust your partner is coming from
the best place like I don't think in
hindsight that he ever really trusted
that I was coming from the best place
like there was always a certain
adversarialness that I would talk about
like why are we coming from a why is
there adversarialness in our interaction
you know like I am on your side like I
demonstrated this through words through
actions through money like I am on your
side but that's the type of [ __ ] that
ain't got nothing to do with me yo that
has nothing to do with me like there
like I'm sure every broad before me and
whoever you living with now is also
dealing with that do you play sports sh
yes I like I learned that in sports like
my coach would yell at me scream at me
during practice but game time it was
like we all on the same team and all of
this is collectively get to the go
there's a man you got Mama issues you
ain't never going to be able to look at
a woman like she's on your team ever
damn am I lying no you look not at all
not not at all I think I'm like having
such a and I say that as some let me can
I just say something real quick I say
that as someone who it took me who had
daddy issues years to be able to look at
Brothers like oh you're on my like in a
Rel in a romantic relationship oh we're
on the same team because I had the
adversarialness too and then I had to
get over my [ __ ] to be like no that's
not my like that's you're not coming at
me we're we're doing this together we're
doing this together and that's how I
came into this that was my last
relationship like I had that
breakthrough of like oh
like I can wholly care about you without
it putting me in danger cuz I got me
yeah and what you said is I feel like
what what people will do to manipulate
you especially if you're mature enough
to recognize your own trauma your own
issues you're going to therapy they
could look at you and say see you got
all the issues you have all the problems
you need to get yourself together and
then they'll act perfect but they'll use
that to manipulate you and I've seen
that so many times we've had people
write in to where it's like the man is
truly manipulating them making that girl
or playing the victim essentially saying
that like you're the one doing
everything wrong right and you have all
the issues you need to go to therapy I
don't need to go to therapy we don't
need to go to therapy together it's
you same I've lived in same same and I
felt
so this person was someone from my past
so simul to like your Dynamic where we
dated when we were so much younger and
so it we entered it with a lot of
euphoria like oh this is so a noal the
story so good oh my
gosh but it was probably I don't know
maybe 10 or 15 years in between the time
and then we reconnect and I have like
I'm in therapy I had been through
therapy I had identified so many things
and one of the things that I had was
trust issues again because similar to
you daddy issues abandonment issues so I
inherently distrust I'm 40 oh these are
father issues now yeah these are father
at 40 they become father
issues his father issues and um I I
admitted that to him in a time where I
felt like we had gotten to a place I
felt safe to say like yep bow yep yep y
I was like you know I have trust issues
and I want you to know that because I
want you to give me Grace when it
appears and I haven't my you be
emotionally intelligent self a facing I
just want Grace when it happens and once
it happened it was totally used against
me it was wielded against me when truly
he was like you know like me not calling
you for 9 hours when I normally would
call you is that's not I was I mean what
do you mean like see that's your trust
issues like that's weapon it and I was
like the fact I wish I never told you
this like it is literally being used
against me as a weapon and and then that
makes you clam up even more then it
almost feels like it's undoing until you
learn that that can then be used against
you until you learn that it's like oh
now I just need to go back in my show
now I didn't trust my father I didn't
trust any of the men up to this moment
and now I can't even I don't even know
when I'm supposed to feel safe because
what I thought was safety wasn't safety
it's like how do you know when it's a
truly safe space like that's a a real
question that I I'm asking you whether
you can answer it or not but I feel like
had he said to you okay let's let's get
down to brast tax like me not calling
you for 9 hours do you feel like that
may be part of your trust issues I feel
like even just broaching it that way
allows you to
self-explore and if you're
like no it's not [ __ ] you usually call
me a night hour on patterns you know
then the the safe space is in him
trusting that you are that you are a a
valid ex examiner of your own beh
behaviors yeah yeah yeah and like
someone should be able to watch and see
through action if someone does that
right are you a valid examiner of your
own behaviors I will tell you
that in my relationship in my effort to
try to like create safe spaces one of
the things that I know that used to
happen was for whatever reason like he
just wouldn't say things that were
bothering him until they were
retaliations so it wouldn't get said but
then now that I have something that's
bothering me it's we're going to deflect
by talking about this thing Y and so to
try to curtail that my so I'm a root
person right I'm not going to talk about
the branches I'm like the root of this
feels like you don't feel comfortable
sharing things in the moment when they
upset you why is that so let's talk
about that and then I was like so what
if we do a thing where every day at the
end of the day because for the most part
like we would go to bed together um
I was like what if at the end of every
day like we have a safe space where we
like share whatever is on our chest for
the day yeah and we also like share
whatever gratitude we have for each
other for the day and that was me trying
to make like a space that we both know
is nonjudgment space like I'm coming to
the space like all right whatever the
[ __ ] tell me I got I got know I'm
saying and no surprises so like these
are the types of things that I was
trying to like employ for our Wellness
because I do feel like at this point
especially if you're in your 40s trying
to be in a relationship and it's like
new like you need tools like not I mean
everybody needs the tools but like we're
so [ __ ] up we we need tools yeah and
because we're so
conditioned by moving Al yeah alone yeah
we're not used to being in tandem yeah
yes and I think some people come into
the relationship thinking that you'll
just like figure it out get with someone
and yeah and figure it out or that it'll
just be an attachment you know like I
know that there were certain things with
him that he seemed to just not grasp
would shift if you're with somebody yeah
you know like even just basic stuff like
if it's 5:30 a.m. and you want to go for
a run so be it but like can you be quiet
about it cuz I'm still asleep oh so I
got a tiptoe yes it please I mean but
that's like why wouldn't you want to
like nobody's saying like don't go run
yeah but like maybe you put your shoes
like your sneakers by the door in the
morning right like it's a big enough
house maybe you go get dressed in the
other room or something you know like
but it's just that kind of
thoughtfulness that comes with
partnership and that's comes with
successful relationships or really
healthy relationships is they put each
other first if you're constantly
thinking about the other person then I
think you'll have a healthy relationship
but what you said is important cuz I was
that type of person like not sharing
things and I realized that I was doing
my own relationship a disservice because
my wife would think nothing bothered
me because so she would even go harder
on me and like Express all this stuff
and she's like oh you're fine like I you
can take the brunt and everything and
I'm like I can't and she was like well
why don't you share why don't you share
the things with me why didn't you
because I don't want to be extra I don't
want to upset the apple cart well it's
more I think it was my sports background
like the mentality of like if you're
interested on the sideline but if you're
if you are on the field I don't want to
hear you complain about nothing you're
not on the field you're in a
relationship I know but in my mind
certain things is like you just suck it
up and just do it like you don't got to
and it doesn't bother you as much it's
like all right whatever I'm just going
to do it all right whatever I'm just
going to do it all right whatever I'm
just going to do and I think your
condition as a man sometimes too to not
complain or even sharing about certain
things is not it looks wack it looks we
it looks weak yeah so it's like no I'm
good but I would constantly say things
and then she'll come at me or give me
this Perfection complex which was really
damaging for us early on is that she saw
me as perfect because I never complained
about never anything never said I had
any issues never said I had any problems
so the moment I did something wrong
which is just a normal thing that people
do because I'm not perfect it was like
all hell broke loose and everything was
wrong and every and I'm like just
because of this like just because of
this you're mad at me but I set the
standard because I never told her I had
any problems never told her I had any
issues I made it seem like everything
was great but I was hurting inside
because I'm like I understand that you
have a lot of things that you're going
through but like what about me like what
about me but it's like you got to say
something in order for people to know
that there's something wrong with
absolutely and don't you want like the
support you know what I'm saying I mean
I feel like the other part
do to unlearn that I guess unn cuz it's
not hard to do it's just hard to unlearn
it because it's been positioned and then
even with the effort of trying to like
let men know like no really you have so
many men who are like quit trying to get
us to share our feelings like there's
like movements yeah I literally saw a
comment the other day that was like men
don't fall for this cuz the moment you
let it down she's never go I'm like do
you know how wildly scary that is like
yeah I just feel like
that's that all connects to this idea
which is a really imperialist idea and
it's at the end of the day it's not even
just imperialist but this idea that
women are really only like meant for
property value and that we are not fully
like thinking breathing vessels and the
idea that you would trust someone to
birth the baby that you would give
everything to but not to handle your
feelings is Bonkers but it's also like
women we also need to be very practiced
at how to handle feelings because we're
in the same patriarchal system and we be
perpetuating that [ __ ] too damn
[ __ ] why you crying you know or damn
[ __ ] why are you crying you know
you know the ratchid demics like it's
like stop and I feel like the softness
that we all deserve for each other we
have to give for each other like I know
that even in being able to say like okay
um I have an issue with something like I
would be met with like I don't want to
be like you I don't want to be somebody
who complains or who has an issue with
things and like he's looking at me like
there's something wrong with me for
stating when I don't like something ET
but that all goes back to your trauma
yeah because you grew up in a space
where when you did that you were scolded
for that right and I just think that we
all have so much to work through so much
and and also that it's a human
experience it is not a I say this so
much on the show it's not a woman
experience it's not a man experience
like we all need to be able to be like
let it out we all need to have room to
do that like you have tear duck my guy
it's it like keep your heart Three
Stacks keep your heart it's okay if you
cry God literally made you to do so um
so on Cat Williams interview on uh that
show on CLI Shay he was like
saying uh he had said something in
passing that a lot of men were like
catching latching on to even though the
the thought got expounded upon they just
latched on to this first little part
where he said a lot of women don't get
men because they are acting like men mhm
right okay I remember this so then I
asked my like Instagram like so men I
just want to hear from y'all I mean so
many women felt the need to chime in I'm
just like I didn't ask y'all we also got
to stop that we got to do that's part of
making a safe space right yep and so
many men were like listing the ways in
which that the ways in which they felt
women act like men and all of them
had examples that were simply just
things that are toxic toxic masculinity
like you know just being competitive you
know just um trying to trying to run
[ __ ] you know trying to question things
and I'm like this is if this is women
acting like men is it okay when men do
this yes yes I remember this post I
remember this post and like no answer
none I mean the issue is that what we're
taught as men well a lot of men think
that the title of leader or being a man
is a title that's just given I guess and
not earned like when it comes to like
relationships so if a man is like you
should submit to me he's like because
I'm a man just because because this is
my gender you should submit to me and
give up all control and have me lead but
if it's like if you haven't
proven that I can trust you if you
haven't shown up consistently time over
time over time over time why would I
submit to you why am I why do I have to
submit that that is a weird word like
it's like why can't we support each
other and know that you have your
strengths and I have my strengths like
you're [ __ ] balls does not give you
leadership skills bro that's very true
like I can tell you like very true
there's things that I'm really good at
that like my partner is just maybe not
good at like but there's also things
that they may be really good at that I'm
not good at and it's not even anything
gender based I'm a really effective
leader I am an MC I move crowds right so
like if we had to be in a situation
where I got to move [ __ ] you know move
crowds like so because you're the man
we're going to expect you to be better
at that no we got the move crowd like so
you don't think there there should be a
teered structure in the household I
don't even understand this is Bonkers to
me like I just
don't I don't know why that's necessary
because we have seen time and time again
when we actually talk to our elders that
that isn't actually the real way that
things were working like in some like
okay the man had this like status that
was given to him by by Society but then
in one household like granny was
actually handling all the bills you know
and actually running all of that in fact
Grandpa couldn't even read so he can't
count the money he doesn't even know
yeah right y then you know you have
other household where it's like okay the
man's supposed to be the one who's the
farmer but granny was the one who
actually had the green thumb you know
what I'm saying and then I just think
that when we look at like this idea that
men are at the head of the household I
think I think that that's like the idea
about that is protectiveness ETC but I
don't know why that has to be contended
with the head that to me ends up being
about
dominance and I feel like that because
that's what patriarchy is patriarch is
about dominance and I know [ __ ] in the
comments right now like see that's why
she's single and it's like yeah that is
exactly why I'm single because we live
in a society that hasn't caught up to
women like me bars and I know that and
so many women comments are like yes
because there's there are men who have
caught up and they are in loving healthy
relationships with women who are bad it
B it r r yeah yeah I think so too I I I
just I think there's no one siiz fits
all you have to do what works for your
household if that structure that him
here you there kids if that's what works
for y'all right out great but that is
not the blanketed you cannot just paint
that with a with a big brush you can't
even when we just look like people just
love to throw things out there like what
about
Africa and I'm like okay so there would
be households you know that had like
three wives right but it's not always
the first wife who was the most loved
right or who was the most skilled or
whatever like we are humans we are so
complex like there is no just like you
know um blanket way of putting things
and for the most part those efforts that
have been made were made to control
people like Henry VII literally started
a whole other Church
because [ __ ] wouldn't let him getting
get married to am Bolan like they'll
just change rules when it doesn't fit
that doesn't work he was married like
completely married the lady was in Spain
like we married and he was like nah I'm
trying to get a divorced they were like
you can't get a divorce not by the
church of no I think he started the
Church of England they were like by the
Catholic Church you can't get divorced
he was like watch this watch me work
then started a whole other church just
to marry a woman that he beheaded
so like what are we it's not funny but
it is it's just the way you said it so
ultimately like all of this stuff is
really um malleable yeah you know it's
it's malleable like it's only in place
for like this the little the little
people because the the people at the top
making the decisions about what we get
to do CH it however they want to that's
my point I'm still trying to digest that
all cuz it's overwhelming to think like
oh so we do have
Choice like even gender which is a whole
other topic than this episode but like
even gender is aaz it's literally a
madeup thing like it's just a construct
and we live in a society that has
accepted that construct and so thus
people are like well I like that
construct so let's hold on to it but you
still have to acknowledge it is a
construct though it's just that you like
it yeah it just fits it's work it works
for you it's worked for a long time I
want to go back to this smart woman dumb
girl like thing I wanted to talk about
that too why am I so good at my work and
so bad at my house why like what are
what are because clearly I almost jumped
out of my chair because I've done it
I've done it and I do not want to repeat
it but you know what it made me think
about and this um it was an interview I
can't remember where it was but I
believe it was Tyler Perry who was
talking about like their with women in
his that he knows that are very well set
up like they have everything they have a
great career they have money they're
very wealthy the only thing they don't
have is a person and they are with a man
who is oh really good to them right good
to them based on his his definition but
they can't like contribute financially
and I think sometimes that that's such a
limited go ahead sorry it's it it is a
very very limited like contribution but
also a very limited like perspective
around the relationship because you
don't really know no that's what I was
saying yeah not the contribution part
but a limited perspective yes it's a
very limited perspective but I feel like
that those women or or cuz I'm going to
put myself in that group too clearly I'm
not a millionaire by far but often times
I have out earned the men that I've
dated I've and not for any other reason
than I made better choices perhaps or
maybe I was just in the right place at
the right time maybe they just weren't
afforded that whatever the reasons were
and I found that in majority of those
dynamics that dumb girl thing
overpowered or just like oh I'm really
smart and I know how to process this and
I can fix him and I can push him in this
direction but that was a dumb thing I
thought I was actually you think that
was a dumb thing sometimes yeah because
I was I was like think that was a dum
thing make more than I don't think that
was a dum thing not no not that because
he didn't make more than me but when
that was the dynamic I felt like I just
need to bring him along like I just need
and and he wasn't even showing that he
should have been yes he wasn't yes
yes it was the it was the I feel like I
can because I don't really I don't need
you to help me pay my bills I don't need
you to contribute to this so that's cool
you could just kind of lay stop doing
[ __ ] for people they didn't ask us to do
it for them or they don't do it for
their themselves that same yeah just
like that's a whole circle back exactly
like I'm over here loving you more than
you're loving yourself yeah like but I
I'm I mean the smart woman's um girl
concept is really just
this idea also that like the skills that
make us effective in our work life
aren't helpful in our love
life I'm like I remember a scenario
where I
was having a conversation with a brother
where I was toe-to-toe with him in terms
of like he's saying something I'm like
well you know then I have a retort
because I know what I'm talking about
and he just got so Kur fuff um and he
was just like oh my God like I just
it's just it's too
much and I was like what is too much
he's like I mean I'm trying to talk to
you and I was like yeah I'm talking back
to you but I wasn't emotional like it
was like we're just
having I mean I I would say it was
heated but we weren't like raising our
voices or anything but like I was
keeping up
yeah and um he was like it's just you
know you're just like you're just doing
too much and that made me emotional
because that made me feel like damnn
like I'm literally just talking to you
and it's just and now I'm getting
insulted right so then I started crying
well now he know what to do once I
became an emotional blob of a girl now
it was now you can have compassion now
you can like see where I'm coming from
or or now you even care to see where I'm
coming from and that made me feel like
oh so you need me to feel you need to me
you need me to be like lowkey in smaller
place than you like you need to me you
need to feel like I'm impaired even
though I'm not but like you you need to
feel like that to be able
to handle me what's that and so like
that felt like when I was in my smart
woman phase I was too much right when
I'm speaking to you logically and we're
having an exchange and I'm you know I'm
responding to what you're saying very
clearly and thoughtfully no this is this
is how I sound right I sound like I
don't have a vagina or boobs or anything
I'm just an AI machine but now that I'm
over here
like like come here baby now let's come
yeah come here girl I got you don't cry
sweetheart don't cry sweetheart he was
from Brooklyn um yeah like I just you
know what else y'all do in that smart
wom dumb girl face y' don't listen to
your home
boys cuz they be trying to tell you A
lot of times like listen a little bit
ain't it and then y'all will just go I
got so many home girls you tell them
like bro is not it at all he he lying to
you but then y'all just no let me think
well no when you were doing it you were
lying but he's a great
person I had a homeboy
who so you know like the folks on the
street that are unable to get mental
health help yeah will label them like oh
like that's crazy jod or etc etc but
they be saying real [ __ ] yep I had a
homeboy who who was unable to get mental
health help and he like you know was
just having like episodes and he pulled
up on my mom's house one day and started
telling my mom like yo you got to get
her away from him like her her light has
dimmed since she's been with him like
her crown has shifted whatever and I was
like what who is he first of all I'm
like why you pulling up to my mom's
house like you know but I and I didn't
know that at that time that he was in a
mental health space I thought he was
like on on shrooms or some [ __ ]
nonetheless if I'm being honest either
way I would have been like whatever yeah
um but he was right he was right he was
right but you're so right and now I
actually now I go straight to my boys
like my homeboy saved me so much time
recently because I hit him and was like
how do you feel about this person and he
was like oh that's a cornball like
that's a full-on cornball and I was like
okay okay in what fashion like talk to
me how you got today so I don't have to
ask you again I'll just know how to
figure it out my own so he like ran it
down now did I still proceed absolutely
but you were now aware so now when the
corn ballery showed up I didn't talk
myself out of it got I was like oh
that's what he was talking
abouty is yeah he was a cornball we be
trying to help y'all I don't get yall
just be it's that glaz
of like no it's
hope yes it's hope like we really want
to be loved and want to love like it's
so funny like people be asking people
like oh I'm sure your DMs are blowing up
no they're not no it's just an
assumption that people have
quiet quiet quiet my DMs are full of
Palestine and puppies like those are my
DMs like there's nobody and anytime a
man does come in my DM they're so wild
it's extreme it is like a dicture I had
a man come in my DMs recently and was
like um you need to date a regular [ __ ]
and I was like actually I've done quite
a bit of that um and I'm not regular so
I don't know why that would be what I
need to date uh your shade is so good I
just it's just so good don't pay
attention Okay I just remember when you
did your uh documentary here DC and you
were talking after and you were talking
about your investment in black in black
men brother I should have returns by
this point okay I have invested in
that's why when people say wild [ __ ] to
me like a man is hates black men I'm
like check my record you know you know
how the politicians be like check my
voting record I'm like check my money
record okay check my time record I
should be getting Amazon gift cards from
women who are with these men now saying
thank you for the time that you put into
Hussein you know I mean like that's
where it should be like no I've given
[ __ ] careers literal careers I mean
like all right go up in the world be
somebody like that needs to be your next
um that needs to be your next skit like
you know the
commercial
experiencea I feel like you need to do
that like if you've had the benefit of
being upgraded and taken care of by
Amanda seals listen and they know who
they are they know who they are welcome
I have listen it's and sometimes it's
monetary sometimes just educ
oh yeah like it it can be so
much just just game you know just even
just like you should get a therapist
right and like now they're like in
therapy right but I mean I've also had
the benefit too of like Exes who became
homies and like seeing their growth and
that's also like really great because
we're able to continuously like show and
see each other like you know Elevate but
I just feel like
there's this idea that
one that like women are turning down
like so many great men and I'm just like
that's not I don't think that's what y
think it is like that no cuz I'm I'm I'm
not turning down Great Men um I'm
turning down the men that should be
turned down I'm turning down the ones
that are unqualified I'm getting turned
down
like by whack [ __ ] like by ones that
shouldn't even be turned down should
even be
then you question yourself oh I'm
absolutely in that phase right now
yourself like what is that possible um
not as fly as I think I like I had to go
back to therapy for a number of reasons
but also because I was like oh like my
self-esteem is shot yeah shot I know
when your backup is like nah I'm good
that proba you mess with your selfesteem
like somebody you always knew like man
if I wanted to I never had backups but I
will say that like at this point all of
us have that person we know can call the
can be like nah you still the badest and
you're like thank you it's when that
person's that's what it actually is it's
when you're your person it's not making
you actually feel better cuz typically
you can go back to that person and
they'll like you're like yeah I am yeah
I'm the flyest and now they said it to
you and you're like well you actually
might want to consider some things so
how do you remain hopeful like do you
like I know that I am at this point
really
no hopeful for what like who knows the
next time I'm going to have sex like
really let's be real who knows I mean
let's be honest I mean if you wanted if
you just wanted to have sex and man you
could have sex yes you could like stop
like like like we're we are not going to
do that we have standards I think so
yeah you could like like like the sex
that I mean just I don't want at this
point it needs to be the sex I want okay
understandable yes I understand thinking
[ __ ] game is just a waste of time okay
it's like I rather Snickers I get that
said what I'd rather ever Snickers than
like waste the waste the cookies on like
something that doesn't deserve it I
honly you were say like [ __ ] with a
hard R and I was like what is she saying
he said I'd rather have a Snickers no
seriously sometimes I would just rather
be home under the blanket like I I don't
even want to do the sport of like
playing a game just to have a quick
little sex moment like I got that like
one person that from the past that you
could always go to that just yes still
you know what it is you're in your 20s
like your past is you're barely out of
your but your 20s is
yesterday last year was your 20s so like
your past is very like short and most of
those people are probably still in that
same part of their life I'm now 42 so
like my past like people have moved on
in their lives like people are in
marriages yeah you can't just go back
and understand what I'm saying like
we've moved out of that phase like the
whole phase everybody was in the at one
time together now there may be some
scragg and you're looking at them like
no don't even know why I did it back
then maybe if uh I'm okay no like I
tried to talk to a politician for a
moment but then it was just
like his stances weren't where they need
to be you know what that's what actually
debted it but what what should have
debted it was when he was like you know
I'm going to come to LA and like take
you on a date and I was like oh wow like
I deserve that so yes that would be
lovely and then I was like where do stay
when you come to La he's like oh I'm a
Marriott kind of guy I was like oh
that's what's up there's actually a
Marriott like around like my way so you
know that'll be convenient to like stay
over here to go to dinner and stuff and
so later in the conversation I was
talking about how like since the breakup
I was actually like painting my house in
the colors that I wanted to because in
the relationship he was always like Oh
I'm a minimalist so I was being
respectful of the fact that we're
sharing a space and he was like so you
got all these rooms and I got to say it
to
Marriott make it make sense dog sir that
should have been the end also you know
okay the number one reason that [ __ ]
holler at me that they'll tell me is
because they feel challenged by
me and I do not want discourse I want
intercourse like I don't know what that
is but I have had multiple men be like
yeah like what turns them on about me is
like they feel like there's going to be
some aggravated like there's going to be
a tussle they want the tussle yes and so
then when I don't give that because
contrary to what people believe like
when I'm with a man I don't speak to
them the way I speak about the
occupation of Palestine yeah yeah yeah
which people think that like the passion
that I have about that like yeah I'm not
speaking to my man with that tone when
I'm then I don't think they understand
that you're actually irritated too like
if you're speaking in that manner so if
they want you to speak to them in that
way you it's not an enduring thing it's
like I'm responding to something so like
they when they don't get that from me
like for some reason that's what they
are wanting but I'm showing up in
softness they will then try to trigger
it yeah so they'll neg me you know what
negging is yeah so they'll try and neg
me and like that was wild to experience
like we were on the phone and and like
when he he like this dude he had called
me when I was driving and I was
listening to a tri Quest record and so
when I answered the phone I was like
back in the days on the boulevard of
Lyndon we used to kick routines when the
presence was fit he was like uh you're
rapping that's so
annoying he sound like a diva he just
wanted to he just wanted to
argue like that's you know I remember
like we were and this over the course of
just one week and then we're on the
phone and he was like I was like you
know
um I would love to send you some videos
about Palestine because I feel like
there's like information that you're
missing that could be really helpful and
just forming an opinion because he was
saying that he just didn't know how to
think about it he just didn't know how
to feel about it and I was like you know
I do feel that you you know um respect
my mind and he went for now
girl I just o so so did he still get a
chance after that after that comment no
oh yes yes because I have self-esteem
issues MH yeah smart smart woman smart
woman dumb girl also because I'm so
trained um some in part by you people on
this internet to not come off as like
too hard or Too Short or too sharp so I
will allow mistreatment to not look like
I am a certain way yeah you'll take it
it's very dangerous yeah you'll take it
yes and so you know I'm trying to be
better to myself of like so then like we
ended up stopping talking because he was
like um actually I'm going to run a
scenario by yall cuz cuz you're probably
going to be tell me I'm tripping but
it's fine um can't wait to let's hear it
this is what this show is about real
scenar scenario so okay so first off let
me just tell you that it first the first
reason it ended was because that next he
had called me in the morning at like on
a Saturday morning and I um well no I
had texted him and was like Hey I told
you about those links I was going to
send you you you said it was okay so I'm
not sure what you don't know so I'm kind
of like shooting in the dark and he
replied back and said well you're
mistaking you're confusing me saying
don't know how to feel about it with I
don't know okay and I said oh I guess I
just assumed you didn't know how to feel
about it because you needed more
information information and he said well
that's not an assumption you should have
made he smart ass that happened yes he's
a very smart so this happened on text
and he calls me okay and he's like man
you starting early and I was like well
the the genocide didn't stop because I
went to sleep so I'm just I wake that's
how I've been living since October 7th
like I go to sleep I wake up I I'm like
consuming right like this is where we
are living and I don't know when this is
going to air but like I mean I came in
to do this today and saw that they were
like yeah we're about to obliterate the
rest of the Palestinians so like if
you're into trying to understand
something like you're in it and I'm a
cancer we like yeah long story short he
was like well yeah like I felt like you
were making an assumption and you're
really just trying to send me these
videos because you want me to think
about it the way you want to think about
it
and I was like well there's really only
one moral way to think about this and
ultimately like you're not going to [ __ ]
me if you don't think that way about it
right and I'm just keeping it a buck
about the [ __ ] okay and uh he was like
well you know what I don't even got time
for this and then I was like I got
click
click so then when we clicked I text him
I said you know I guess there's cuz
there was just things we just didn't
have in common and I was like you know
gu we have more things in common than I
thought including like our ideology on
integrity and he replied back and
said don't tell me about integrity when
you won't even have a
conversation now mind you I had been
trying to have this conversation right
clearly so I let that rock for a day and
then the next day I texted and said I
would like to have a conversation
because you know I'm a glutton for
punishment y yep I hate that by the way
though well Dre I'm glad we're friends
um um
so I said I'd like to have a
conversation and he never responded
until I did Celebrity Jeopardy then I
get a
text I get a text on Celebrity japanes
should I should I have responded no but
I am a clutton for
punishment father
issues you better sing
it that's my 90s version um so we got on
the phone and we actually had a very
interesting conversation where he did
take accountability for his behavior and
all of that and was just like you know I
really
didn't handle that properly yeah and I
thought so many times about calling you
and then I would stop and just for the
men out there like don't say that to
people keep that to yourself that sounds
crazy yeah why are you not calling
what's going to happen what's the worst
thing that can happen I don't answer I
don't answer yeah that's it do you think
I'm gonna scream on you like I was like
it's also a phone call so if I do you
can hang up I think he was maybe trying
to excus the absence by saying that he
had thought about it multiple times
possibly no that's not a brownie Point
nope so then he goes well you know I got
to tell you this but you know I'm G say
it I'm G just say it one time you know
what I'm saying if you tell anybody
I'mma deny it I'm like What's He about
oh [ __ ] he was
like it was very difficult not to call
you huh boy I this is a very he trying
to run games let me know when you ready
for the answer to the real love scenario
did he say it like that just like that
he was trying to run game you see the
voice change don't yes I hate ITA Hey
listen he got the let me stop I don't
want to go jail sorry let me not do any
what did I do I didn't you didn't see
anything cut that is that your people no
no are you no I'm not he's like I me
fight
me I played football so it was that was
it I just was
like so anyways we got off the phone
with
the to me we got off the phone like okay
so we're we cleared the air yeah and we
will resume yes okay because I am a
Redemptive person by the way yeah so
like some of it is my glutton for
punishment but some of it is like I
really believe the best in people and
like we all have missteps so the same
way that like yeah maybe I shouldn't
have hung up the phone I'm asking for a
have a conversation
right so the next day I don't hear from
him all day mhm this is my real life
scenario okay I y'all are gonna be like
I told you she was crazy so I need to
get prepared you I texted him and was
like Hey did I did I not hear from you
today because you were busy or because
you were like questioning whether or not
you should hit me MH and he was like a
man it's just been a crazy day you know
what I'm saying like there's just been
so much going on mhm mhm now let me just
say this my home girl is a gynecologist
and one time I called her and she
answered the phone and said hey I'm
elbows deep in a uterus can I call you
back so I don't ever want to hear
nobody tell me who cares about me like
yo I was too busy like and we got text
and DM and all the things now did you
forget that happens right like happens
to me oh my God I kept saying I kept
telling myself that I was that I need to
hit you and I just kept getting pulled
into I I
apologize no I was just so busy you know
what I'm saying etc
etc so I thought about that y'all and I
wanted to be okay with that but I wasn't
okay with that okay
because I feel like if you know that you
exactly like you said yesterday like
played yourself and you know you
actually acted out of pocket and you
ruined the opportunity for this then to
me I feel like this second chance should
be treated with
preciousness and so if you're not going
to hit me all day the next day and then
say it's cuz you're busy and not even be
like you you up now or or any thing like
that there's no preciousness there and
so I thought about
it and I was like am I GNA sound like a
crazy
[ __ ] maybe and then I texted I said you
know what actually is fine like if if we
were really starting back again which is
what I thought was happening then I
would have expected to hear from you but
clearly I had a different M indication
of what last night's conversation was
and so it's all good like I'll catch you
in the mix he hits me back and says okay
this is a lot and I said
Perhaps Perhaps and he said I'll call
you later and I have never heard from
him since yeah you made the right
decision but he said I'll call you later
and I have never heard from him since
yeah so I made the right DEC decision
yes yes yes but did I sound like a crazy
[ __ ] I don't think you sounded like a
crazy [ __ ] I think that if I was if you
were writing into the show and you wrote
that whole thing in I would have said
maybe three interactions
ago that it was time to be done with it
it was even even like the like the
Redemptive thing I appreciate but when
you were talking about this it made it
made me think about a guy I was dating
very briefly and we got on the topic of
having a child who is trans and they
learned this when they're very young I
was I watched jod Patterson's story with
her her her yes with her her son check
her out on my podcast small doses she's
amazing and I was so inspired by this
and I had just watched this I'm telling
him about it and I'm likeed yes I'm like
this is like and then it just brings up
the conversation like what would you
know if this were you like how do you
think you would handle it as a parent
and his reaction told me I cannot
proceed I cannot go past SC he can have
his feelings about it which as you can
imagine he's like I would not be okay
with it like my child cannot my son
would never he could I would be this he
would have to leave my house way that
folks be okay yes so so with that said
fundamentally we were not on the same
page and so when you had found that out
specifically around Palestine because I
think he was giving off the he was
giving enough clues that he did not feel
the way that I will say this when we had
our redemp emptive convo he was like you
were right about that and I and thank
you for inspiring me to actually get in
the weeds and I and now I understand got
it and being that that's been so many
people's story right like I just had
somebody DM me the other day like when
you said on October 7th what you said I
was so angry with you like I I felt like
you had betrayed me and you know for
three weeks I was just like Amanda seals
on some BS and then I had to check
myself someone in their in my DMs they
said they said they checked themselves
because they were like yeah you've
literally agreed with her on like
everything else so like maybe it's worth
researching and they said that they
literally committed themselves to
research for an hour and with an hour
we're like
oh so that's part of why I was like but
how he was handling it was just real
deal it was too much it's too much like
like you could say like even like oh you
you at it early it's like why even can I
be honest though yes I think that
um there's so okay so I'm a public
figure and that adds a whole other thing
to like my just life right because like
I'm I have to worry about my world and
then I'm worrying about the world and
then I'm worrying about how the world is
worrying about my
world that's a whole other thing that's
a lot and so like dating is like a weird
thing that I don't necessarily have
insight into because it's like it's not
just about if someone has the enough
money or to feel to feel comfortable
being with me it's not just about if
someone has the like intellect Etc or
the positioning so like this was
somebody who seemed like a possibility
because they had like they had an educ
like the education level like they had
like the the um EST they were
established in their career Etc and that
just feels like it's such a small bucket
yeah because it is right so I think I
was still I was trying to like come on
you're so
close yes please yeah and it just but I
don't I think there's just like you said
like there were just so there were just
flags for [ __ ] all of that from the
beginning when you say so you got a you
got a house but I got to sit at the
Marriott [ __ ] yeah like yes because you
should you I'm sorry you should want you
should want to St at the whack about
that you would not have stayed at the
Marriott if you had got your ass here
and had a great dinner don't tell them
nothing don't tell them nothing I just I
you know I have to because so many of us
deserve this like shut the [ __ ] up shut
up show up shut up and show up shut up
that should be a t-shirt shut up and
show up it's so real like you don't need
to like you're all your ego is so in the
way and like what's the goal what I
don't even know know what the goal is
for some of these men anymore I don't it
used to be [ __ ] and now it's clearly
not it's not that either because the
amount of [ __ ] they're doing to not get
[ __ ] is beyond my scope of
comprehension well maybe they don't know
how to but how that that no these are
men that I know that they had to have
got they're getting I know people whose
[ __ ] they've been
in I know some of the [ __ ] they got
just like so I you know it's it's a very
kind of like where do we go from here
well my perspective on it is I don't
mind you giving the extra chances okay I
don't think there was a lot at stake
like he wasn't in person it wasn't like
y'all were having sex or anything like
that it was just a few conversations
that were exchanged so even a second
chance is just an additional
conversation and then I can see you know
sometimes you get into situations and
you may have thought like dang I had I
put that person on short leash and maybe
I didn't give them a chance so then when
he came and apologized and said you know
after looking it over you're like a
redeeming quality maybe some people need
time right some people need a little
time to just digest things and figure it
out these are the things I tell myself
yes um but I think once you got to the
point to where you were done I think
that's fine because I think there's
standard things that people have in
relationships that we universally say
you shouldn't shouldn't do like
communicate trust is a big thing in
relationships you should be honest but I
think I think that's why I said that
probably through interaction but those
main things everything else is just
particular to you and what you like and
I think that when it came
to you know the guy that you were
talking to there were certain things
just internally for you that just didn't
work so you saying I'm really should
have ended it and this is a lesson that
I will carry with my S moving
forward people telling themselves all
the time yep within the first
conversation he referred to himself as
an [ __ ]
but I'm a nice [ __ ] interesting and
then he like told a story where he was
mean to some like he was mean to someone
he was dating and I was like that was
mean and he was like well we're you know
we're friends now so like we cleared it
up and I was like yeah but like that was
mean yes and that is actually when I
should have been like Amanda this isn't
for you was he somebody who's known you
for a long time or was he more somebody
who knew I guess your persona or saw you
publicly and that was how you you guys
came to know each other CU I wonder if
he said that thinking that he was
somehow relating to you or no he wasn't
saying that to relate to me like he was
just we were on a panel together okay at
an event and
um I mean I think
that I I think that he was maybe
relating to like you mean like by him
calling himself an [ __ ] like oh
you're an [ __ ] nice [ __ ] I think
he may have thought that like you
understand right like just based off of
the Persona right it's like I genuinely
can't remember the context but you know
what something that's also a weird flag
for and I I won't call I won't call it
necessarily a red flag but it's a weird
flag when you're a public person is I'm
not just a public person I am a legit
artist like I want to shout out my
homeboy wilmo big wilmo reminded me the
other day he was like I just want you to
remember because it came up like in his
like Facebook reminder thing he was like
your HBO Comedy Special came out on this
day five years ago you have been working
at the highest level for 30 years like
you started on Nickelodeon like you've
been working at the highest level for 30
years he was like that's not a common
thing that people have done and I I've
never thought of it that way and I was
like godamn I am an icon absolutely and
I have a breath of work yes so when
someone is trying to holler at me and
it's like yeah I don't want to learn
about you or your work like I want to
learn about you from you like I don't
want to look at your work that's like a
weird flag because I am
so I am an artist I've lived through my
work so for you to not want to explore
that that's not my ego that makes you
want to know my work like that's my
heart yes yes yes my heart is my heart
it is because you are an artist that it
is very different because I have the
perspective of I don't want I don't want
you to learn me from that but I'm also
not an artist right like I have a
corporate 9 to5 outside of this don't
want you to learn me through that
because that's just business that's
paper that's like no but when you're an
artist it is it is a part of your fabric
it is it is a part of who you are but
some people had that balance of like oh
if I'm talking to somebody like you I
can't approach you like a fan you know
but you don't have to be a fan but you
do have to be a fan yes you have to be a
fan yes you do have to be a fan not like
who's the coolest celebrity you met yeah
like I don't mean a fan like you know
you're going to interview me at dinner
but you best believe I'm I'mma Be my
nigga's biggest fan if you ever run into
my ex ask that ask about me I am his
biggest fan I will sit here today and
tell you that's one of the most talented
producers on this Earth he a [ __ ] and
he ain't [ __ ] but on an MP talented yes
but that man is gifted as [ __ ] you know
and I will never take that from him yeah
that man is a skilled gifted audio
engineer is that part of the frustration
when it comes to the relationship too
it's like I see the potential there
that's not even potential that is actual
that's actual well how that can
translate into providing more for you I
guess how you can take that Talent cuz
some people have the talent and ability
I was just looking at him like why
aren't you [ __ ] me like why aren't you
doing this for you like there would be
times where he's playing beats in the
house I'm come I come in the room like I
remember crying one time because I was
like I I don't know why the like I wish
the world could hear your music like
you're so good yeah like you're so
[ __ ] good like he did some of the
music for my documentary and then we
broke up and he dropped the [ __ ] ball
and left and left me hanging and quit in
the middle of it and I was left with
having to learn how to line up the [ __ ]
like I had to learn a whole new skill
because of this [ __ ] and I just want to
shout out my other homeboy Willard Hill
who swooped in and actually help me
complete the music because artists don't
leave artists hanging and that's why he
will never be truly successful because
you can have all the skill in the world
but if you don't have the heart in your
art it will never actually win and I
don't care what kind of breakup we had
you don't leave my [ __ ] hanging because
that's your art it's your art like you
don't want that out there you feel me I
wouldn't feel good in your in your heart
like to just leave that un like there's
I don't care what you know like and so
but I would never like take that from
him and I just feel like
there's something so pure in like
artists creating you know and so when
you get to meet somebody that does that
if you don't see that in them then you
actually aren't really approaching them
and you have such the opportunity with
someone like myself to know that before
you even get to me yeah you have a cheat
code to like actually learn me in a real
way so like why not why not explore that
why not explore that that you know don't
don't don't tell me about like and I'm
not and that's the thing it's like I've
had to accept like Amanda you had a
different experience in this life like
you are a public figure like it's not
the same you can keep trying to act like
you in the peanut gallery [ __ ] you not
you're not you you not so what's the
correct approach like if somebody
PowerPoint presentation some was like
I'm interested in Amanda do they slide
in the DMS do they come up to you in
person when they see you like how should
they
approach a PowerPoint presentation and
what money and escrow that's what she
said I had a gang driver who picked me
up from the airport and I don't know how
we got in this conversation she play too
much got
power so slide one shows you uh where I
was born I grew up in a two parent
household um like this is what I this is
what I would like for us M like on slide
10 we get to the Future this is the
other thing too and tell me how you feel
about this real love scenario
scenario we manda's got to do the theme
song We'll we we'll pull the money
together we'll start a okay that's
that's on the mic it's on the camera on
the camera you heard it okay um I was
the first like you were the first and
the first
second
um
um at this point in my life I'm not
interested in people who are approaching
me
casually like I'm not saying like I like
lowkey like you need to be pressed mhm
what does that look like like that looks
like consistency and
intentionalism that looks like I want to
guess if you like me I want to know you
like me mhmh you're already arriving
liking me yeah you're arriving liking me
yes right like we're not doing a like
you're going to figure out if you love
me mhm but you're already
arriving with like yeah because you've
seen how I move in the world you've
already observed you've already done
your your Instagram forensic
specialist right like you ran it down
yeah you NCSI my my my damn in like you
already see what it is yeah you've
already like said like that's the type
of you know woman I you know I would
like to entertain and I say this because
a revolutionary woman's I say this
because a revolutionary woman's love
will not be one passively oo baby like I
don't exist in this world passively so
do not come at me passively and don't
give me another
task please what's your cash app so I
can send you a little offer real quick
like don't add to my tasks you know like
our interaction should be a relief you
know when they say be there be his peace
be my peace be my peace baby I will be
your peace yes all I want is to be a
[ __ ] peace please
how her for me I'm too far away get it
for me thank you thank you like please
I'm a peaceful [ __ ] baby okay what what
can I'm a part of what can we watch on
the couch click like that's the click
I'm in can we sit on the couch you want
Kettle or butter can we share right can
we share the blanket can we put our feet
together yes let's watch another one L
let's cuddle do you want to stop no like
part of the reason me and stayed
together so long is cuz had an
incredibly extensive watch habit like
one thing about us that we got right was
[ __ ] know how to watch a show yeah
yeah you know shout out to the py
[ __ ]
blinders like that [ __ ] would be down
to W like when we started pey blinders
it was like we would watch that [ __ ] on
the plane like whatever like he was down
for that but I think that that's
something I've had to just become very
honest with myself and not like shade
myself for like no like you you show up
ready yeah so show up ready I'm not
saying you're showing up to live with me
or to be like in a I'm not even saying
we're showing up to claim each other
yeah yeah but show up with
intention and on a basic level show up
how show up knowing how to treat yes me
yes you know that's why when home he was
like I will come to LA and take you out
because that's what you deserve I'm like
correct that is right and I will be here
and I bought a dress for that outing
damn I returned it okay fa fair enough I
do have a date dress I have a look for
the for the first date I go next one yes
okay good some [ __ ] going to end up
taking me out on Dat somebody it's going
to happen I want you to keep that hope
because it's going to happen and let me
tell you that dress is a [ __ ]
problem it is it is I mean I'm just
saying um I'm an in shaped kind of gal
and it's together it's going to do the
things but I just think that that's
something these are like things I've had
to like be honest with myself about
right like I have really good homeboys
and I was telling my homeboy the story
of the of the of the the Redemption
conversation everything and when I told
him that he said that was a lot he was
like so this is my homeboy who's French
shout to lant he was like so it's a lot
okay like sometimes you are a lot so he
was like I mean that's part of you like
that's what someone is getting and they
are going to get a lot like for them as
well like in a good way like if you had
a lot person sometimes like it's like
that is part of like what makes you such
a great person like you are that always
kill that we got the Florida one on at
part one yeah we did amazing French on
part
two this why she consistency because
she's consistent that's actually very
true yeah yeah I'm I've had to be
consistent because I've been an only
child and I've been like
alone charting this course for so long
so I mean we've been doing my podcast
Mal does for six years like we haven't
missed a week love it like it's cuz
consistency
in a relationship is caring yeah yeah
for sure it is you know and a lot of
women actually don't want a lot of women
I'm not saying all of us but a lot of
women don't need your money we need
security and consistency is is tied up
in security yes it right like there is
something it's
reliability that'sa say it's protection
not in the physical sense but in the
emotional sense consistency protects
your feelings so that's why when a [ __ ]
don't call you for n [ __ ] hours tell
him his response should be hey my bad I
can see how that could make you feel une
wasn't serious about you so that's why
he didn't do that that's why he didn't
do it it's it's true it's very true
hence we are well for other reasons too
because God Rest is soul but prior to
that would be a reason why you're talk
that would be a primary reason but it
ended prior to that you know because he
he just why you trying to make me laugh
at something that's not funny I'm sorry
okay apologize I'm a comic I will laugh
about dark [ __ ] but that's the thing
it's like yeah I if if if you aren't
consistent you you won't be consistent
if you're not consistent in the early
phases in the dating phases and to me
where it should be easier to be
consistent consistency should be a part
of your character it should have nothing
to do with me you're consistent in
paying your bills every month or are you
or or are you but that that's when
things start off with games and being
weird just is not like when I met my
wife there wasn't games there there were
things we need to work on but I didn't
have to guess if she liked me or if she
was committed to me or if she wanted to
spend every moment with me that wasn't a
guess but if you're in the mo in the
beginning parts and you're guessing
about those things it's like but I will
tell you this and I know that this isn't
of course like everybody
but a lot of
the societal setup of dating ends up
requiring you to do that because so many
are
programmed to feel like anything other
than that is you being extra or you
being needy or being a lot you know and
um as opposed to you just being
deliberate yeah right so a lot of women
we're told like don't do that like no
you got to really act
un ET and then men will tell you like
yeah you got to do that don't let these
[ __ ] think that you like them off top
it's everybody playing games everybody's
playing games and so I'm someone who's
never I've never played games so that's
also like I said earlier like that's why
you ain't with nobody because I'm not
playing the game like I'm even in like
the business of Hollywood I realized
that I needed to find a different course
because I don't want to play the game
and it's not like I can change the game
change the game yep
so like create your own space so you
know and then and then the lesbians
watching are like create your own space
and I'm like I just don't I don't I
don't want titties on my titties I'm so
sorry I can't talking about the business
side of things I am like you like I feel
no because all the lesbians be in my
like DMs like come over to this
side it's not that easy like I can't if
I could I probably would don't want to
eat [ __ ] and I don't it's just that
simple I don't want a woman to eat my
[ __ ] I just
don't Lord what was I about to say I
forgot it that fast you
oh no about um the games like I feel
like we're from a generation where it's
like I remember the Press thing was a
thing like if you weren't outside my
house if you weren't like making sure
you got to the phone by a certain time
to call me before I couldn't take calls
because it was 9:00 like I came from
that tribe where you wrote the letters
you brought the flowers you did you did
all the extra stuff and because the
games have been so prevalent today like
the way that I hold on to Hope cuz I
don't ask you that question but the way
I hold on to hope is to go back to the
things that were like that like
nostalgic music where like they are
begging I literally made a playlist
called black love signed him and it is
filled with songs of men that are like
baby please I love you
girl baby literally and I listen to that
when I'm feeling I okay will cry for you
tonight before I let you go can I get a
kiss good night you just begging yes
listen they just wanted to know your
name can we talk for a minute girl I
want to
know name
babying that the entire playlist is like
that so when I'm feeling like I don't
know how this going to work out I go to
that cuz I'm like these men they exist I
know they exist they they exist well you
know what the issue is they exist is
that the man who's way below your
standards or way below you know where
you are with things he's intimidated by
you no he's not and let me tell you he's
no he's not cuz he's in my DMs them
[ __ ] are not intimidated they're
actually very confident and in a
relationship they wouldn't be able to be
in a relationship with you fair and then
the guys who are at where the level
let's say career all that stuff like
that they're desired by so many right so
sometimes those men can I add another
caveat for that yes they also have all
of those things but they're smart men
dumb
men yes they don't have emotional
intelligence to be with someone who is
on their intellectual level but
sometimes when they're in that position
of being highly desired it's almost like
you got to court me I know and show me
that you are worth my time because now
the like there is that that standard
that you describe is no longer right so
you have that in between of that the
lower dude in the top dude and they see
the so many of those dudes below that
they're like I'm the catch yeah so know
the CCH I ain't got a court we going to
the on the UN popular opinion we not are
we going there you want to go there
here's what my thing is about we going
there well not even like this thing
about
courting is I think that's like a that
term itself ends up really being
attached to like this old-fashioned idea
of acquiring property um when ultimately
it's
just I want to show you who I
am and I want the opportunity to learn
who you are at the same time yes that to
me is what it should be yes and like I'm
somebody
that it's not a money thing but for a
lot of men it is like they need that I
need I don't need that I'm so serious
that I don't need that but they need
that and so since y'all need that you
better have that yeah okay that's for
you to feel secure and good about
yourself in this relationship that so
[ __ ] it then let's just do that make
sure you got 50 racks in escrow before
we even
start because you need that do that for
you because I would hate for for this to
get ruined off of something that you
already knew you needed off R like I
mean I just this [ __ ] is so complicated
and it's so difficult it's not simple
and we've also been trick to think it is
like why can't y'all just get together
because it's not that simple we are
complex
computers we don't even know our own
programming you know and some people
have not downloaded a new iOS for a long
time my operating system is tough not I
think in theory it's simple but in
application it's very
difficult whatever that's so when people
say it's simple they think like oh all
you got to do is do this and yeah you
could say all you got to do is do that
putting a dick in a [ __ ] is simple
everything Beyond and even that requires
a certain level of wetness if we're
being honest it
does you know it needs some processing
it needs some
processing man can we Prime can we
Amazon Prime like you know moistness is
preferred I'm just
saying all of this [ __ ] as I've gotten
older I've actually just changed even
the way that I cuz people ask me for
advice all the time and I've just even
changed the way I deliver advice because
I think that I was coming from a the
school of the way so many others give
advice which is these generalities and
ultimately it's
like you have to understand you to even
be able to take advice say that again so
yeah a lot of us are really just asking
for permission we're not even asking for
advice we're asking for permission to do
the thing that we already know that
we're going to do very true right or
we're asking asking for affirmation for
affirming like I'm asking y'all like am
I a crazy [ __ ] right and I mean
whatever y'all say I still think I am
that's okay because if I'm saying that
I'm like okay I'm just trying to learn
but I I just I just feel like we're
we're getting better at talking and I do
think that is really like we're getting
better on these spaces I think some
podcasts need to actually go to hell
aged because they're not having real
conversations from a solution space or a
love space it really is from an ego
space which is not helpful to anybody
but we have to get we have to continue
to get back to talking like even on my
radio show I do like a word of the day
and for some people they may think
that's perfunctory but the reason why is
because I'm like we need more words
that's a good word Prof funter 10 points
for Gryffindor
we need more words to describe like one
of the things I can tell you
so so many people I know in my
life that were very close to me only
know three words happy three feelings
happy sad mad if that's the extent of
your emotional
vocabulary what are we really going to
be able to do because even if I'm just
slightly annoyed you think I'm mad so
you're responding to that baby I'm just
miffed yeah let it go you know what I'm
saying then it's like okay happy well
happy has like a lot of phases and if
I'm not giving you this that doesn't
mean I'm not still pleased yeah yeah
they see it as a switch versus like a
spectrum you need the Spectrum to
examine yourself to know how to respond
to things Etc so that's one way when we
see mindfulness being taught in children
it's so beautiful because it's giving
them language to exist in a complex
World your feelings are as complex as
this world and if you can't identify
them then it's always going to be
overwhelming for you and now you're
trying to be in someone else's world how
is that g to work how you know so like I
love seeing men these days who
are excited about learning the adventure
of themselves like the emotional journey
of themselves like I think that if more
men specifically black men saw that as
like the true warrior effort like we
would be in such a different place as a
society of black people in our families
in our family structures if so many more
black men
saw um providing as something more than
just monetary uh support and security
but like providing emotional support and
Security in your home like that is so
much of what we need for like the black
family structure to grow and I think
that people are like no we need marriage
Etc and it's like listen some people
just aren't compatible mentally and
emotionally but they were physically and
so they made a person but that doesn't
mean you can't still have compatibility
as parents that's right and creating an
emotionally secure place I can tell you
that at 42 I'm in therapy and I'm trying
to figure my [ __ ] out because I didn't
have two people that could comp
committed to do that yeah do it for you
yeah I will that 1,00% you don't got to
stay with the [ __ ] but stay with the
parenting yes work with that was my
experience my parents were divorc ever
since I could remember but always were
cordial great never had any issue so
when I hear people say
like we're staying together for the kids
but it's like super unhealthy I'm like
have you ever talked to a kid who grew
up in that unhealthy environment with
both of the parents there they would
tell you like no I'm good y'all could
y'all could go you can feel all of that
my ex's kids were like we were so happy
when they sat us down and said we're
getting divorced we were like great good
finally we are done we finally glad
y'all got here because it was it was it
was rough for them for a long time yeah
yeah well listen speaking of it advice
and small doses we got a quick little
segment to wrap things up M small doses
of dating advice there we go I don't
know if I'm even you're qualified you're
one of the brightest Minds in the world
literally literally I've actually learn
words from you the world in the world
interal this is light work this is light
work all right so here's the scenario
two people they're really good for each
other like on paper very like matter of
fact this works out you you went here we
do that but the sex isn't
great should they try to stick it
through maybe explore non monogamy or is
the sex just a deal breaker and they
should let it go I mean how how deep
into this are they like couple years
have they talked about this yeah they
just it's a lack of Attraction it's just
really not there they're attracted on
everything but the physical all
yes you like it I love it I mean I just
you know because now we're in this whole
world of like well what does what does
partnership really look like right like
they might decide like you know what we
don't need that we don't need that but I
want to get it from somewhere else and
if you're okay with that and I'm okay
with that then so [ __ ] be it okay
but like sometimes it's I feel like no
like I I do need that or sometimes you
try and convince yourself that you don't
really need that and it's like if you
got to convince yourself you're not you
then I don't know if that's really
sustainable or that's like the most
healthiest situation I agree but I think
that we are in a society that does allow
for a lot more versatility in what
partnership looks like and that's a
conversation away I agree all right next
one your homeboy we talked about about
having really good friends he does not
like your man he admits this after yall
in a relationship he never says anything
while you're dating but y'all get
together and he's like you know I really
don't like it and he starts to make it
obvious like when you all you're around
him with your dude how do you handle it
he don't come around my dude no more
yeah that's just you can't do that yeah
we still friends but you just I don't
bring you around okay easy enough all
right next one but also like why don't
you like my [ __ ] because Dre has said
that we don't listen to our homeboys so
also why you don't like him like why you
tell me this earlier okay but I feel
like as your homeboy you got to be
respectful you know a certain level of
respect yeah you you can't I I even feel
like it's weird to just outright say
that maybe you just say like it's just
certain things that or he did this I
don't like how he treats you when it
comes some of the things you told me
makes me feel uneasy about him but just
to like flat out say that is like but
where are camera
also don't be telling me everything bad
about your person after every bad about
your person and then you surprise when I
don't like them right that's true oh
yeah that's true I hate that give me
give me a mixture you telling me
everything that's wrong the gam good and
the bad you come to me every time
something wrong and then you like you
don't like them now no I don't like
[ __ ] I don't understand why you do why
you like them all right I feel like I
already know what you're going to say on
this one but you're in therapy you
yourself but your partner won't go
because they don't think they need it oh
at this point that's a deal breaker yeah
everybody needs it you know you don't
need it all the time mhm um
um and you don't need it in the same way
like some therapy is talk therapy then
there's raiki there's float therapy I
mean there's a myriad of ways but I at
this point feel
like you can't be a conscious person in
this world and not be
constantly like taking care of your
brain it's like being a basketball
player and not going not working out not
going to
Mass no I don't mean that I mean like
you have to when you're a basketball
player like you have to take care of
your body like you have to get massage
you need to be in the whirlpool you you
may need to get you know you need to ice
like this is just upkeep yeah it's just
maintenance
so at this point I would love to meet
somebody who's in the maintenance level
of their
healing you know who already has
identified like yeah they've gone and
done the Deep work the deep root work MH
and they may be in a new phase of you
know but they they identify
like yes this is this is the phases but
ultimately it's
like I don't know that I have met enough
men in a romantic space let me not say I
don't know I have not met enough men in
a romantic space that like
women they like
[ __ ] but but they
don't like women they don't they just
tolerate them yeah like they don't think
we're
cool you know what I'm saying like they
don't think we're on their level like
they don't see joy in us like they don't
see our uniqueness as additive to their
individualism like and so they don't
have like
a inherent kindness that they extend to
us and I feel like that's been something
that a lot of my female friends have
like extended my homeboys are men who
I've never felt
like I wasn't equal to and then when I
did it was like oh well we're not you
know what I'm saying but they have
always
regarded me as a full person yeah and
like shared in my space right so I I've
I've I've had men who are like I don't
want my girl to be my friend my girl is
my girl yeah that's common that's really
common my girl is my girl my friends are
my friends that's very
common
and you know I'm
I'm I'm really just
like it's
it there's just a kindness that I think
a lot of men don't have for women and
I've experienced it in a real way like
why are you talking to me that way yeah
you know like why are you treat like why
why you would never treat your [ __ ]
like this like ever you would never
treat your [ __ ] like this why are you
treating me this way why do you think
this is an appropriate
interaction you know like stuff like
that is the part that makes me not as
hopeful yeah because I don't think
Society is interested in nurturing
that and I want at the very least our
black community to be to say well them
crackers over there may not be about
that but we are we have to be we have to
be we have to be I just hate hearing
that man yes it's very disappoint I I
feel like I've had a balance I feel
definitely feel like I've had a balance
I've experienced that wholeheartedly
where it's like while you just want it
for what it can do for you not because
you feel it brings Joy or just
camaraderie and love and respect but
I've also thankfully friends and men
that I've
dated and I'm thankful for the men
specifically that I dated because they
helped me understand my worth they at
least introduced it to me so that I can
start exploring it for myself but then
also like giving me that hope that like
oh yeah y'all might be a small group I
would say my first boyfriend ever MH was
that okay that's what's allowed for even
you know what I'm saying like my first
boyfriend Maris like I was treated with
respect with respect I was treated with
kindness like I was never pressured you
know or pushed to do anything um you
look so devastated it just doesn't make
any sense cuz I mean if you talk to men
who are truly married and happy they'll
tell you that it is an amazing thing
when you find the right person but then
I look at the guys that maybe you're
talking about and it's there for them
but it seems like they don't want to
have that countability and a
responsibility that it takes to be in a
relationship well yeah because the right
person means that you're going to have
to like do stuff and be yeah be
accountable like like I had someone tell
me recently they were like yeah like I
want to I'm going to have to leave your
company because I don't have the mental
health to work at a job I care
about what yeah they were like I I
realize that I need to work somewhere
where I don't care about it because it
will stress me out working for someone
who I actually like care about the work
and I was just like wow and I think that
can be related to
I'm not even just G to say men just like
people in relationships like that's part
of the whole like I don't want to have
feelings you know mental health is like
the stomach ache of the second grade
it's like when you trying to get out
when you trying to get out of school
yeah like my stomach hurts a whole other
episod get out and it's like people use
that mental health word just fly it
around don't they abusing abusing it
that was it those are my those are my
small doses thank you for participating
I appreciate that we appreciate those
those those are those are the ones see
you handled that like a pro very well
like a pro you know it's
um it's a weird thing to be not a weird
thing but it's actually been an honor to
like now be in this place where I've
been on the earth long enough and I've
been visible long enough where people
like trust yeah you know so I'm I try my
best to always be like incredibly
thoughtful yeah about my responses to
things and
um you know just understanding
of how many of us don't have sounding
boards and don't have
Community um and like so like with my
patreon like for a long time like my
patreon was just like somewhere that I
was just like posting like adree
episodes of my podcast but um I've
started treating it as a community and
it's been really dope to just see how
folks are feeling nurtured by that like
they're telling me like you know this
chat that we have and you know the
conversations and the different postings
it's it's creating more of a dynamic
space outside of like this social media
[ __ ] right and even over there like I
feel like I'm getting to learn more
about how to even be more present in
that way and with the podcast with small
doses you know I've I've learned over
these years like small doses has been
therapy for me yeah it's it's been
therapy for me I mean we changed the
category right yes we did we changed the
category from comedy to self-improvement
education should have been should have
been but I'm in a new cycle like a new
season as a creative and
really um entering like I I feel like
when I did the podcast last time like I
was already embracing that like you are
in this independent space but now it's
like really that like where Hollywood is
kind of just like make sure I get my
health insurance you know
but I
I really take like my
work seriously and I appreciate that
people like take me seriously um not you
the [ __ ] in the comments who's going to
say I don't but not you um but I feel
like it's it's just a like the work in
progress that I am like I've had to do
like in front of people and like it's
been it's it's been a ride and y'all are
on the ride and I just signed my next
book deal this week oh congratulations
we on the ride again let's
go so yeah I got to write another book
that's amazing well I'm happy for you
and proud even if it doesn't mean much
but very very proud of you it's amazing
don't ever let nobody tell you that that
don't mean much everybody wants to be
told someone's proud of them yeah very
very proud of you very very proud of you
honored to to sit with you for a second
time and you can come back whenever you
like whenever you like whenever you like
whatever you like please can I plug
something I was to say say please plug
away where to find you all the
stuff um you can find me on Instagram at
Amanda seals you can find me on YouTube
at Amanda seals TV I do lives uh on
YouTube now where I'm really trying to
just expound upon like more like
information based content so like my
podcast I feel like is
more it's themed whereas like I I'll
like pick a headline and be like we
going to bring somebody on like to talk
about this you can also check out the
Amanda seal show uh we are every day
wherever you get your podcast we're also
syndicated in select cities and you can
go follow us on YouTube and Instagram at
seals set it and you can catch me on
tour so you can go to Amanda seals.com
catch me on tour I'm in various cities
I'm not sure when this is going to air
so check out when I'm coming to your
city and you can sign up for my
newsletter so that you don't miss out on
any of these things that's going on and
last but not least you can subscribe to
my patreon you can get there at the
amanda.com or just go to patreon and put
in my name um um my small doses podcast
that airs weekly we will have video
episodes of that on my patreon as well
as bonus episodes that I have now
started to do on my patreon and all of
this is really a part of creating an
ecosystem that is supported by
Grassroots and by the people and not by
the um Hollywood System that controls
people and that's why I get to sit up
here with a kefia and say free Palestine
word and happy Black History Month
put the fist up right there oh my God
that was so good that was awesome thank
you so much you know I appreciate you
yes ditto same same always coming
through Amanda seals ladies and
[Music]
gentlemen and